Ivan Dimitrov

ABOUT

I am a backend software engineer who is a fast learner, enjoys challenges and enjoys working in a high energy environment using modern technologies. I am used to applying agile methodologies and breaking down user requirements. I am not afraid of making decisions and taking responsibility. I have also experience with enterprise projects using Java and Android.

Professional experience

StageAI, Sofia

Senior Software Developer

May 2020 - Present

- ▷ Solve complex tasks mainly using GOlang and PostgreSQL;
- ▶ Provide and help others to provide clean and efficient code;
- ▷ Supervise the working processes applying agile methodologies;
- ▷ Breakdown tasks and requirements.

Software Developer

Jan 2018 - May 2020

- ▶ Develop various web application using mainly with Golang, SQL, REST and Graphql;
- ▷ Deliver high quality code;
- ▶ Follow best practices like TDD, refactoring and code standards.

Musala Soft, Sofia

Software developer

Aug 2016 - Dec 2017

▶ Worked as a contractor for Experian maintaining their existing project using mainly internal tools in the Java ecosystem.

Junoir Software Developer

Aug 2015 - Aug 2016

- ▷ Developed native android applications with Java;
- ▶ Maintained Java Enterprise application using JSP, maven, OracleDB;
- $\,\vartriangleright\,$ Maintained hybrid mobile application with Javascript and a pache Cordova.

Game developer-intern, Varna

Software Developer

Aug 2014 – Sept 2014

Sep 2017

SKILLS

- ▷ Golang, PostgreSQL, GraphQL, RESTFul services, GIT
- ▶ Team player, Attention to details, Organizational skills

EDUCATION

Technical University, Varna

M.S. of Computer Science Sep 2013 – June 2015 B.S. of Electronics Sep 2009 – June 2013

CERTIFICATIONS

Oracle Certified Professional	l, Oracle
-------------------------------	-----------

Agile Software Developement, The Business Institute

Apr 2017

Managing Team Performance, The Business Institute Feb 2017

Oracle Certified Associate, Oracle Nov 2016